Let me now talk about two bootstrap components
接下来我们将学习两个 Bootstrap 组件
than can be used to display content on your webpage.
这两个组件都是拿来显示内容的
In particular, about Bootstrap Panels and Wells.
它们分别是面板和 Well
Sometimes, within your webpage you may want to highlight a piece of content.
有时你可能会想高亮表示 你网页中的某些内容
So that it's more clearly visible to the users.
从而用户将会更有可能注意到它们
Now, panels and wells are two ways that you can highlight
而面板和 well 正是两种你可以
content with a new webpage so that it's more easily noticeable to the visitors.
用一个新页面来高亮显示某些内容的方法
Panels as you see, allows you to display a content
面板 顾名思义 允许你在一个盒子里
inside a bounded box, as you see in the picture here.
显示一些内容 如图所示
Now within this boundary box you can have a simple boundary around the box.
你可以为这个盒子设置一个简单的边界
That would be a standard panel.
这也是一个标准的面板会做的事
You can also have a panel heading in place.
你也可以为你的面板加一个标题
So in the example that you see on the screen, we have a panel heading in place.
在这个栗子里 我们通过设置 class="panel-heading"
And within the panel heading, you can specify the content
来指定一个写标题的 div 块
to be displayed in the heading by using the panel-title class.
在这个 div 块中还需要一个设置了 class="panel-title" 的某个 h 标签
So here in this example,
在这个栗子里我们的用的 h 标签是 h3
I am using the panel-title class being applied to the h3 tag there.
而在 h3 标签中的内容自然就是我们想要
And you can see the display off the panel title in the panel on the right hand side.
出现在面板标题中的内容
The panel body itself can contain any HTML content.
而在 panel-body 的下面则可以包含 任一个 HTML 元素
Now in this example,
在这个栗子里
I am using a description list in order to
我用的是一个描述表
show some data about the restaurant itself.
通过这个描述表我可以显示餐厅的一些信息
Now this is one way you can use a description list.
而事实上显示信息确实是描述表的用法之一
In particular, I am using description list with the class
注意到 我这里对描述表设置了 class="dl-horizontal"
dl-horizontal, so that the term and
所以这些信息都分别整齐地排列在了
the description are displayed in the same horizontal line here.
同一水平线上
For a panel, you can also specify a footer.
对于面板 你还可以定义页脚
If for your specific use situation if footer makes more sense,
如果你确实需要用到页脚的话
then just like you applied the panel heading,
你完全可以像定义标题那样
you can also define a panel footer to be applied to the panel.
去定义它
Our next Bootstrap component is a Well.
接下来要学习的 Bootstrap 组件是 Well
A well, as you'll see from the example here
正如这个栗子所示 一个 well 就像是一个
is like a bounded box surrounded with a light gray background here.
有着淡灰色背景的小盒子
Inside this well, you can include any content.
在 well 里面你可以加入任何内容
Now to use a well, you just apply the well class to a div.
使用 well 的方法也很简单 只需要设置一个 div 的类为 well 即可
And inside the div, whatever content that you include will be enclosed
然后在这个 div 的下面 你可以封装进 任何 HTML 元素
inside this light gray bounded box as you see on the right side.
这些元素将会在一个淡灰色背景的盒子中呈现 如图右侧所示
In this example, you can also see me using the block quote to
在这个栗子里 我还用到了 blockquote 来
display a quotation from the user.
显示我对用户言论的引用
When you use a block code, you will have the content being formatted,
当你应用 blockquote 时 你的内容将会 像图中那样被格式化
as shown in the picture there with
同时一个垂直的线会出现在
a vertical bar on the left side to highlight what content.
整个 blockquote 的左侧
For the block code, we can also specify a footer.
我们同样可以对 blockquote 设置页脚
There, you can specify the source of this quotation.
通常我们会在页脚处表明所引用语句的出处
Wells can also be qualified by using the Well LG and
well 的大小也是可以设置的
Well SM classes to define a large and a small well.
只需要将 well-lg 等等设置进类就好
What you see in the picture is a default sized well.
图中所示的 well 是一个默认大小的 well
If you would like a larger well, then together with the well class,
如果你想要一个大点的 well
you can use the well-lg class.
只需设置 class="well well-lg" 就行了
For a small well, you can use the well-sm class.
同理如果想要小一点的 well 的话就用 well-sm
Finally, we'll move on to the exercise for this lecture, where we will look at
接下来 我们将会进行下一个练习
the use of Tables, Panels and Wells in our webpage.
在这个练习里 我们将会在我们的页面中 实现表格 面板和 well
So we will create style and
我们将会定制一个 Bootstrap 表格
present some tabular data in the form of a Bootstrap table.
并呈现一些表格数据
And we'll use Bootstrap's table classes to style the table.
定制的方法自然是通过各种各样的 Bootstrap 表格类
We'll also include a panel and a well onto the webpage.
最后 我们将引入一个面板和一个 well 【翻译 - Carefree0910】